Welcome to session nine,
欢迎来到第九节课，
we're gonna talk about strumming today,
我们今天要谈的是扫弦，
many good aspects about strumming,
很多好的扫弦方法，
different ways to get the best sound out of your strums that you can,
让你的扫弦发出最好的声音，
pretty much we've just been doing single chords at this point
我们在这一点上一直在做单和弦，
or single strums when it comes to chords,
或者当谈到和弦时，单扫弦，
now we're going a little bit more complicated,
现在我们要变得更复杂，
start making a little more music with it.
开始用它来制作更多的音乐。
So we talk about good strumming technique,
所以我们谈论好的扫弦技巧，
I'm going to teach you a couple of simple strumming patterns,
我将教你几个简单的扫弦模式，
that you can incorporate into your own playing
你可以把它们融入你自己的演奏中，
and we're going to talk about getting creative with strumming,
我们将讨论如何创造性地扫弦，
getting beyond just the techniques of it
超越它的技巧，
and starting to get a feel for it just inside of you.
开始感受它在你体内的感觉。
In the how music works section,
在音乐是如何工作的一节中，
we're gonna cover intervals,
我们将讨论音程，
intervals that are in the major scale,
在大调音阶中的音程，
and intervals that are not in the major scale
不在大调音阶的音程，
and messing around with those intervals a little bit,
并稍微调整一下这些音程，
so we're going to learn some more songs
所以我们将学习更多的歌曲，
and put all that we've learned together to make some music,
并将我们学到的所有知识放在一起创作一些音乐，
I hope you're ready to go,
我希望你们准备好了，
I'll see you there.
我会在那里与你们见面。
Okay, let's talk about strumming,
好的，让我们来谈谈扫弦，
now up to this point,
到目前为止，
you've pretty much played one chord or one strum for each beat
你已经为每个节拍弹奏了一个和弦或一个扫弦，
or sometimes we'll just give a whole note for each measure that chord is in,
或者有时我们会为每个和弦所在小节使用一个全音符，
we're going to talk about strumming, what strumming,
我们会讨论扫弦，什么是扫弦，
strumming is playing a rhythm while playing the chords,
扫弦是在弹奏和弦的同时弹奏节奏，
so instead of just playing a G down here,
所以不是在只弹奏 G ，
we're gonna add a little rhythm to it.
我们给它增加一点节奏。
By the end of this session,
到这节课结束，
you'll be able to do that,
你将能够做到这一点，
because that's one of our simple rhythmic patterns,
因为这是简单节奏模式之一，
that we're going to be talking about simple strumming patterns.
我们将要讨论的简单扫弦模式。
Okay, so just adding some simple strumming your chord playing
好的，只要加上一些简单的扫弦到你的和弦弹奏中，
helps you to start making music
就能帮助你开始创作音乐，
and that's what it's all about.
这就是它所要做的。
Okay, so let's first start talking about technique,
所以我们首先来谈谈技巧，
in our right hand, not much that needs to happen,
在我们的右手中，不需要太多的事情需要发生，
but a couple key things you need, you need to think about,
但有几件关键的事情你需要考虑，
you need to hold your pick, nice and firm,
你需要拿着你的拨片，漂亮而坚定，
okay, you need to have,
你需要有，
because when you're strumming, you don't want that pick to be too loose,
因为当你扫弦的时候，你不想让那个拨片太松，
when you get a whole awful lot of pick noise,
当你得到一大堆拨片噪音，
which is not a good sound,
不是好的声音，
need to hold that pick nice and strong,
你需要握住那个拨片，好且有力，
you want your wrist to be loose,
你想要你的手腕放松，
a lot of times folks will think,
很多时候人们会想，
as we're getting through some of these exercises
我们正在做一些练习，
as you speed up the tendency is to really tense up that, tense up that hand
随着你加速，这个趋势会让你收起手腕，
to where you if you bring this wrist in
你把手腕往里拉，
and you tense up this whole forearm up here,
把整个前臂往上拉，
okay, you gotta get faster and you get all excited about that
你要变得更快，你会变得很兴奋，
and you get all tensed up
你会变得很紧张，
and that's not what we want to do,
这不是我们想要做的，
the motion is not that,
动作不是那样，
the motion is more like you're flicking something off of your hand,
动作更像是你在弹掉你手中的东西，
imagine if you had something on your hand,
想象一下，如果你的手上有什么东西，
and you were trying to flick something off of it,
你试图弹出一些东西，
that's the motion,
这是那个动作，
your wrist is loose,
你的手腕是放松的，
you have to still hold your pick,
你必须仍然握住你的拨片，
but your wrist is loose as you're doing that,
但当你这样做的时候，你的手腕是放松的，
okay, you want your arm motion,
你想要你的手臂动作，
let's talk about what your arm is doing,
让我们来讨论一下你的手臂是什么样子的，
your arm is like, think of it like a piston on in a in an engine,
你的手臂像是，把它想象成发动机里的活塞，
it's always going to be going down up, down up, down up, down up,
它总是下上，下上，下上，下上，
in some of these examples,
在这些例子中，
I'll be I'll be telling you different combinations,
我会告诉你不同的组合，
whatever combination I tell you,
无论我告诉你什么组合，
it's always going to fit into the pattern of down up, down up, down up, down up,
它总是符合下上，下上，下上，下上的模式，
I'm never going to, I'm going to tell you do a up, when you're in the cycle to do a down,
我永远不会告诉你弹一个上，当你在向下的循环中时，
in vice versa,
反之亦然，
now that may seem like you really have to think about it a lot,
看起来你需要好好考虑一下，
as you get into it and speed it up a little bit,
当你进入，并加速的时候，
you realize there's no other way to do it,
你会意识到没有其他方法可以做到这个，
then being consistent with the downs and the ups,
保持与下上的一致，
so your hand is always gone,
所以，你的手总是，
even if I just tell you to do three or four quarter notes,
即使我告诉你做四分音符，
four quarter notes on a G, down down down down,
四分音符在 G 上，下下下下，
there's still a silent up that you're doing,
你仍然在做无声的上，
if you'll notice what your hand is doing.
如果你注意到你的手在做什么。
Now we're going to start talking about making those UPS into strums
现在，我们开始讨论如何将这些上做成扫弦，
and getting a little more complex with that.
并使其变得更加复杂。
Okay, so you're ready for the secret of great strumming,
好的，你已经准备好学习扫弦的秘诀了吗，
here's the secret right here,
秘诀就在这里，
I'll say it probably a dozen times during the course of this,
在课程中，我可能会说十几遍，
KEEP YOUR HAND GOING,
让你的手保持活动，
the temptation would be to stop, make it stop,
诱惑是让它停下来，
and that's gonna make you sound choppy and uneven,
这会让你听起来起伏不定，
it's not going to work,
这不会起作用，
what's the secret,
秘诀是什么，
keep your hand going,
保持你的手活动，
I could play that rhythm like this,
我可以像这样演奏节奏，
it doesn't sound right,
它听起来不太对劲，
it kind of sounds choppy,
听起来有点起伏，
I kind of lose some of the rhythm with it,
我有点失去了节奏，
what's the secret,
秘诀是什么，
keep your hand going.
保持你的手活动。
Okay, now let's take a look at some simple strumming patterns,
好的，让我们来看看一些简单的扫弦模式，
we're going to start very basic
我们将从非常基础的开始，
and then get to some more complicated patterns that sounds a bit more musical.
然后学习一些更复杂的模式，听起来更有音乐感。
Okay, so look at example number one,
好的，看第一个例子，
just on a C chord,
在 C 和弦上，
we're just gonna do down strokes on that C chord
我们要做的是在那个 C 和弦上往下划，
and then we're going to get into eighth notes and down and up,
然后我们要进入八分音符，然后下上，
what you're looking for here is,
你在这里看到的是，
I'm hitting accurate going down on that C chord,
我在那个 C 和弦上准确地击打，
I hit that fifth string down
我拨动第五弦，
when I, when my hand and arm kind of arc back,
当我的手和手臂向后拉的时候，
I hit a few other strings,
我拨动了其他几根弦，
not all of them,
不是所有的，
remember we talked about that,
记得我们说过，
so accurate going down, some of them coming out of,
准确地向下，有些上来，
my hand is always making this little arc right here,
我的手总是在这里形成这个小弧线，
my hand is always going down up down up
我的手总是下上，下上，
and you're looking for smooth even strumming.
你在寻找平稳的扫弦。
Here we go, number one, ready go,
我们开始，第一个，准备，开始，
another measure,
另一个小节，
now the eighth notes here,
现在这里是八分音符，
down up, down up, down up, smoothing even,
下上，下上，下上，平稳地，
let's go back to those quarters repeat,
让我们回到那些四分音符，
down down down down down,
下下下下下，
I'll slow it down a little bit here,
我在这里会慢一点，
eighth notes, ready go.
八分音符，准备，开始。
Very good, okay,
很好，
now let's go to look at number two,
现在让我们来看看第二个，
now I kind of bring those eighth notes
现在我把那些八分音符
and I mix them in with a with a quarter notes a little bit more,
和四分音符混合在一起，再多一点，
okay, we're gonna go from a C chord to a G chord,
我们要从 C 和弦到 G 和弦，
I'll start slow
我开始会慢一点，
and then we'll play a little bit faster.
然后我们会弹得快一点。
Number two, ready, go,
第二个，准备，开始，
C, C, down up, down up,
C C ，下上，下上，
G, G, down up,
G G ，下上，
repeat it back to C,
重复回到 C ，
smooth and even strums.
平稳的扫弦。
Very good, number three,
非常好，第三个，
let's take a look at number three,
让我们来看看第三个，
through some barre chords in here for you,
通过这里的一些横按和弦，
just give a little practice on barre chords,
在横按和弦上做一点练习，
because you can strum on barre chords as well,
因为你也可以在横按和弦上扫弦，
I've mixed the rhythm up a little bit more,
我把节奏混合得更多了，
now when you see those slashes,
当你看到那些斜杠时，
that means you're just supposed to keep on with that same rhythm, remember,
这意味着你应该继续保持同样的节奏，记得吗，
ready, start on an F chord,
准备，从 F 和弦开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
down, down up, down, down up,
下，下上，下，下上，
Bb,
Bb ，
Gm7,
Gm7 ，
Csus,
Csus ，
F,
F ，
let's try that one more time,
让我们再试一次，
a little bit faster this time,
这次快一点，
ready, go.
准备，开始。
Good, now you'll notice,
好的，现在你会注意到，
I used different barre chords,
我用了不同的横按和弦，
for that, you want generally it's easiest to play barre chords,
一般来说，弹奏横按和弦是最容易的，
yeah, from about maybe the eighth fret down,
大概是从第八品以下，
so if I come,
所以如果我，
like in that example, I have a Csus at the very next to last measure,
比如在那个例子中，我在倒数第二个小节有 Csus ，
now I have a choice,
现在我有一个选择，
whether to play a Csus up here or down here,
在这里弹奏 Csus ，还是在下面演奏，
generally, things are more comfortable down here,
一般来说，这里的情况更舒服，
so I'm always swapping those forms
所以我总是交换那些形式，
at which form would put me in a more favorable position to play.
能让我在弹奏中处于更有利位置的形式。
Okay, now we've done strumming with just eighth notes,
好了，现在我们扫弦使用八分音符，
keeping track of our downs and our ups,
继续向下或向上，
now we're going to throw a few ties in it
现在我们在里面加一些延音线，
and it makes it a little bit more musically interesting to listen to.
这会让它听起来更有音乐趣味性。
Okay, so let's start with number one,
好的，让我们从第一个开始，
this is strumming with eighth notes and ties.
这是用八分音符和延音线的扫弦。
Okay, let's look at number one in your book,
好的，让我们来看看你书中第一个，
starts on a G chord
以 G 和弦开始，
and look at that pattern, down, down up, up, down,
看看这个模式，下，下上，上，下，
now don't get to lost in the downs and ups,
不要迷失在下和上之中，
remember your hand is always going down up, down up, down up, down up,
记住你的手总是下上，下上，下上，下上，
so now I'm just going to take out some of those downs, some of those ups,
所以现在我要拿出一些下，一些上，
and we're just going to play the ones that we need to,
只会弹奏我们需要的，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
let me slow it down, down, down up, up, down,
让我放慢速度，下，下上，上，下，
remember your hand is always going down up, down up, down,
记住你的手总是下上，下上，下，
now on a G chord.
现在是 G 和弦。
Let's just do that first measure,
让我们来做第一个小节，
ready, your hand is going down up, down up,
准备，你的手下上，下上，
ready go now,
现在准备开始，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
down, let's repeat that first measure,
下，让我们重复第一个小节，
so there's a silent down in there,
这里有一个静默的下，
down up, up, down,
下上，上，下，
let's slow a way down for you,
让我们慢一点，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
may take you a while to get it at first.
可能一开始需要你一些时间。
Okay, start again,
好的，再来一次，
ready go, down,
准备，开始，下，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
down, down up, up, down.
下，下上，上，下。
Okay, now let's do that musical example number one,
好的，现在我们来做这个音乐示例第一个，
two measures of G, two measures of C,
两个小节 G ，两个小节 C ，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
up, up, down,
上，上，下，
again, down, down up,
再次，下，下上，
now, C chord,
现在， C 和弦，
back to G,
回到 G ，
C.
C 。
Now number two,
现在第二个，
starts with a C7 chord,
从 C7 和弦开始，
okay, remember our good open C7 chord
好的，记得我们的开放 C7 和弦，
and I changed the rhythm up a little bit on this one,
我稍微改变了这个节奏，
okay, so let's take a look at it,
好的，让我们来看一下，
down up, down up, up, down,
下上，下上，上，下，
now let's try with the chord,
现在让我们用和弦试一下，
we'll do it nice and slow first,
我们先慢慢地做，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
up, down,
上，下，
again, down up, down up, up, down,
再来一次，下上，下上，上，下，
down up, down up, up, down.
下上，下上，上，下。
Okay, now let's play that whole pattern,
好的，现在让我们弹奏整个模式，
ready, number two, ready, go,
准备，第二个，准备，开始，
Am7,
Am7 ，
Dm7,
Dm7 ，
G7,
G7 ，
one more time,
再来一次，
keep your wrist loose,
保持手腕放松，
very good, you're going to make sure that wrist is loose in there,
很好，你要确保手腕放松，
if you get too stressed out about it,
如果你对此感到压力太大，
you'll end up sounding real choppy.
你最终会听起来真的很不稳定。
Let's do number three,
让我们来做第三个，
okay, this is the third most common,
好的，这是第三个最常见的，
not most common, but a third common strumming pattern,
不是最常见的，但是第三个最常见的扫弦模式，
you ready, starts on Ab,
你准备好了吗，从 Ab 开始，
down up, up, up, down,
下上，上，上，下，
here we go, on a Ab,
我们开始，在 Ab 上，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
down up, up, up, down,
下上，上，上，下，
again,
再来一次，
got it,
明白了吗，
okay, now let's play the whole line,
好的，现在让我们弹奏整行，
ready, go.
线路准备好了，开始。
do it again.
再来一次。
Good.
好的。
Now the main thing you want to keep a in mind
现在，你要记住的主要事情是，
as you're doing this strumming is
当你做这个扫弦时，
you want to make sure you're keep your hand going,
你要确保你的手保持运动，
make sure your wrist is loose,
要确保你的手腕放松，
as you speed up things,
当你加快速度时，
don't tense up, relax that wrist even more,
不要紧张，放松手腕，
that's what you want to do.
这就是你要做的。
Now, those are a couple of patterns,
这是几种模式，
there's another one on your page as well,
在你的页面上也有另一种模式，
but that's just some simple ideas to get you started on strumming,
但这只是一些简单的想法，让你开始扫弦，
ideally, I don't want you to be thinking down, down up, up, down,
理想情况下，我不希望你想，下，下上，上，下，
as you're trying to play a song,
当你弹奏歌曲时，
once you get used to the flow of it,
一旦你习惯了它的流动，
so once you get these,
那么一旦你得到了这些，
try and not look at the music,
试着不要看着音乐，
and do the same strumming,
做同样的扫弦，
like for number one would be down, down up, up, down,
就像第一个，下，下上，上，下，
so at first when you're thinking about it,
所以当你一开始想它的时候，
let's say we're doing on the G chord,
让我们假设在 G 和弦上，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
I don't want you, I want you to
我不想要你，我希望你，
as you speed up, not to have to think about the downs and ups,
在加速的时候，不必考虑下上，
and that's about strumming
这是关于和弦的，
and the rest is up to you to perfect it
剩下的就靠你来完善它了，
and to get a strong and smooth,
要想让它变得有力和流畅，
takes a little bit of time,
需要一点时间，
don't be discouraged,
不要灰心，
it takes a little bit of time and effort,
需要一点时间和努力，
main thing, relax, keep that hand going.
主要的事情是放松，保持手的运动。
Now let's learn a little bit about intervals in our next section.
现在，让我们在下一节中学习一些有关音程的知识。
Okay, welcome to intervals,
好的，欢迎来到音程，
we've talked about half steps and whole steps,
我们已经讨论了半音和全音，
we've talked about major scales,
我们已经讨论了大调音阶，
we've talked about keys and key signatures,
我们已经讨论了调和调号，
now we're up to intervals,
现在我们到了音程，
well, what are intervals,
好的，音程是什么，
intervals, what I'm talking about is the distance between two notes,
音程，我说的是两个音符之间的距离，
not notes that are right next to each other,
不是紧邻的音符，
like a half step and whole step,
比如半音和全音，
notes that are beyond that,
超过这些的音符，
like if I'm in the key of C
比如我在 C 调中，
and I want to know the distance between a C and an E,
我想知道 C 和 E 之间的距离，
that would be an interval,
这是一个音程，
a C to an F, a C to a B,
从 C 到 F ，从 C 到 B ，
all of those would be intervals,
所有这些都是音程，
now there's two different types,
现在有两种不同类型，
there's intervals that are within the major scale or built off the major scale,
在大调音阶内的或建立在大调音阶之上的音程，
these are called diatonic intervals,
这些被称为自然音程，
diatonic, means inside the scale,
diatonic 意思是在音阶之内，
now, the two different,
现在，两个不同的，
we're going to separate those intervals up a little bit,
我们要把这些音程分开一点，
the second, the third, the sixth and the seventh are all referred to as major intervals,
第二，第三，第六和第七被称为大调音程，
don't get that confused with major chords,
不要和大调和弦混淆，
we're talking about intervals, completely different thing,
我们说的是音程，完全不同的东西，
the second, third, sixth and seventh are major intervals,
第二，第三，第六和第七是大调音程，
we just kind of split those intervals up into two groups
我们只是把这些音程分成两组，
and call them different things,
然后叫它们不同的东西，
the intervals that are left are the fourth, the fifth and the octave, or the eighth,
剩下的音程是第四，第五和第八，
okay, those intervals aren't called major intervals,
好的，这些音程不叫大调音程，
those intervals are called perfect,
这些音程叫完全音程，
I don't know why it's that way,
我不知道为什么会这样，
it's just kind of how it is,
就是这样，
major intervals, second, third, sixth and seventh,
大调音程，第二、第三、第六和第七，
perfect intervals, fourth, fifth and octave.
完全音程，第四、第五和第八。
Okay, now, so let me ask you a couple of questions, a different way,
好的，现在让我问你们几个问题，换一种方式，
if I said in C, what is the perfect fourth,
如果我在 C 中说，完全音程的第四是什么，
the answer would be F,
答案应该是 F ，
the only thing you're listening for is,
你唯一听的是，
when I say fourth, sixth, seventh, eighth, second,
当我说第四、第六、第七、第八、第二，
okay, there's little names that are going to go in front of those,
好的，有一些小的名字会放在那些前面，
that are not important at this point,
现在不重要，
they're going to be important later on,
它们会在以后变得重要，
but at this point, just realized there's a group of major, there's a group of perfect,
但在这一点上，意识到有一组大调音程，有一组完全音程，
so if I said to you an F, what is the major sixth,
所以如果我问你一个 F ，大调的第六是什么，
well, the major sixth in F would be a D,
好的， F 大调的第六个是 D ，
if I'm in Bb and I say what's the major seventh,
如果我在 Bb ，我说大调第七个是什么，
that would be the seventh step and then Bb that would be an A.
那是第七个，然后 Bb 会是 A 。
Now let's talk about the other group, harmonic intervals,
现在让我们来谈谈另一组，和声音程，
these are intervals that are not within the scale,
这些音程不在音阶之内，
they're going to take the ones from the scale,
它们会从音阶中取出，
but we're going to adjust them a little bit.
但我们会稍微调整一下。
Okay, so we're gonna adjust up
好的，我们要调整，
either a half step up or a half step down.
往上半音或往下半音。
Okay, if I call,
好的，如果我说，
and again we gotta just into two groups again,
我们再一次分成两组，
the major intervals, if I raise them up a half step,
大调音程，如果我提高它们半音，
that's called an augmented interval,
这被称为增强音程，
what is an augmented second, augmented sixth,
什么是增强音程第二个，增强音程第六个，
okay, augmented is also used to describe going a half step up for the perfect intervals,
好的，增强音程也被用来描述完全音程提高半音，
so really, if you're going to half step up on any interval outside of the major scale,
所以，如果你在任何大调音阶之外的任何音程上提升半音，
it's going to be referred to as augmented,
它将被称为增强的，
even augmented fourth augmented fifth.
即使是增强音程第四个，增强音程第五个。
So if I wanted to,
所以如果我想，
in C, if I wanted an augmented fifth, let's say,
在 C 中，如果我想要一个增强音程第五个，
that would be a G#,
那将是 G# ，
G would be the fifth,
G 是第五个，
augmented that, G would be the G#.
增强 G 将是 G# 。
Okay, now if I want to go down on the major intervals,
好的，现在如果我想要降到大调音程，
that's referred to as minor,
那就是小调音程，
okay, don't get that confused with minor chords or anything like that,
好的，不要把它和小调和弦搞混了，
in intervals, major if I want to lower that interval a half step,
在音程中，如果我把大调音程降低半音，
that's called minor,
那就叫小调，
if I'm in F and I want the minor third,
如果我在 F 调，我想要小调三度音，
in F, I go to the third step, which is an A,
在 F 中，我走三步，也就是 A ，
but now I'm making it minor
但现在我把它变成小调，
or I'm going down a half step,
或者我要降半音，
then it would be an Ab,
然后它就是 Ab ，
so the minor third in F would be an Ab.
所以 F 中的小三度是 Ab 。
If I want to go down on a perfect interval,
如果我想在一个完全音程向下，
fourth, fifth or octave,
第四、第五或八度，
I refer to that as diminished,
我将其称为减弱音程，
if I'm in G
如果我在 G 中，
and I say, well, what's the diminished fifth,
我说，减弱第五个是什么，
in G, I would go up to the fifth step, which is a D
在 G 中，我会上升第五个音，也就是 D ，
and go down a half step, Db,
然后下降半音，
a diminished fifth would be a Db,
减弱音程第五个就是 Db ，
don't get confused,
别搞混了，
I could ask it this way,
我可以这样问，
in G, what is the augmented fourth,
在 G 中，什么是增强音程第四个，
well, the augmented fourth would be,
增强音程第四个将是，
I go up to C,
我走到 C ，
and then go up one, that would be a C#,
然后再往上走一步，是 C# ，
but now you're saying to yourself,
但现在你对自己说，
well, Steve, that means that the augmented fourth and diminished fifth are the same note,
Steve ，这意味着增强音程的第四个和减弱音程的第五个是同一个音符，
yes, they are the same note,
是的，它们是同一个音符，
but it's called by two different things,
但它是由两个不同的东西来命名的，
if I asked you for the augmented fourth,
如果我问你增强音程的第四个，
you have to tell me C#,
你必须告诉我 C# ，
if you answer Db,
如果你回答 Db ，
that's wrong,
这是错误的，
that would be diminished fifth,
那将是减弱音程第五个，
see how that works.
看到它是如何工作的。
Okay, now let's talk about in enharmonic tones,
现在我们来讨论一下等音，
big word, all it means is that,
大写字母，它的意思是，
some tones like a C# and Db are going to be one pitch,
一些音调，比如 C# 和 Db 是一个音高，
but have two different names,
但有两个不同的名字，
that's what enharmonic tones are.
这就是等音。
The other thing, as we're adjusting these intervals,
另一件事是，当我们调整这些音程时，
sometimes you're going to need to flat an already flatted note,
有时你需要降调已经降调的音符，
what if I'm in a,
如果我在，
let's say, I'm in Eb and I want a diminished fifth,
比如，我在 Eb ，我想要减弱音程第五个，
well, the fifth in Eb is a Bb,
在 Eb 的第五个是 Bb ，
but I want to make that lower,
但我想把它更低一点，
how do I do that,
我该怎么做，
I do what's called a double flat.
这就是所谓的双降。
Here's your assignment for the week,
这是你这周的作业，
now that we've got all that theory stuff out of, out of the way,
现在我们已经把理论上的东西都弄好了，
I want you practice the songs that we have in the book,
我想让你练习一下书中的歌曲，
dealing with the strumming patterns,
使用扫弦模式，
using the strumming patterns that we've learned,
使用我们已经学过的扫弦模式，
some of the simple ones that we've talked about,
一些简单的我们讨论过的，
I want you to complete the intervals worksheets,
我想让你们完成音程工作表，
talks about when in C, what's the third,
讲的是，在 C 中，第三个是什么，
and F, what's the six that sort of thing.
在 F 中，第六个是什么，这类事情。
Okay, let's go ahead and go to the workshop time
好的，我们去 workshop 时间，
and I'll see you there.
我们在那里见。
Alright, let's work out some of these things now,
好的，现在让我们来做一些这样的事情，
in our workshop time,
在我们的 workshop 时间里，
we want to talk about basic,
我们想谈谈基本的，
the basic strumming patterns that we talked about.
我们所说的基本扫弦模式。
Let's go through those,
让我们来看一下，
the first one was,
第一个是，
down, down up, up, down.
下，下上，上，下。
Let's do that together on a G chord,
让我们一起用 G 和弦来弹奏，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
down, a bit faster,
下，快一点，
a little faster, you're doing great.
快一点，你做的很好。
Good, let's play exercise number one,
好的，让我们来弹第一个，
start out nice and slow, then will speed up,
开始的时候慢一点，然后会加速，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
now a C chord,
现在 C 和弦，
back to G,
回到 G ，
try not to hesitate between chords,
试着在和弦之间不要犹豫，
slow and even strums.
慢而且平稳的扫弦。
Good, now let's play a little bit faster,
好的，现在让我们再快一点，
ready, go.
准备，开始。
Very good, okay, now let's go to number two,
很好，好的，现在让我们来看第二个，
starts on that C7,
从 C7 开始，
we'll do it slow first time,
第一次会慢一点，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
down up, down up, up, down,
下上，下上，上，下，
down up, down up,
下上，下上，
do it again,
再来一次，
C7, down up, down up, up, down,
C7 ，下上，下上，上，下，
keep that hand going.
保持手的运动。
Very, very good,
非常好，
okay, number two, a little bit faster,
好的，第二个，稍微快一点，
ready, go.
准备，开始。
Now, ready for number three,
现在，准备第三个，
slow at first, down up, up and go,
先慢一点，下上，上，开始，
again.
再来一次。
Good, now a little bit faster,
好的，现在快一点，
one two, ready, go.
1 2 ，准备，开始。
Number four, ready, go,
第四个，准备，开始，
Now, a little bit faster,
现在，加快一点，
ready, one two, ready and go.
准备， 1 2 ，准备，开始。
Great, now let's move on to our first song,
好的，现在让我们到第一首歌，
are actually the only song that we're gonna cover in this workshop portion.
是我们在这个 workshop 部分要介绍的唯一一首歌。
La Bamba,
La Bamba ，
okay, you've got the single notes to it
好的，你有单音符，
and you've also got the chords,
也有和弦，
let's just touch on those single notes first,
让我们先弹奏那些单音符，
because we've got some rhythm things that we need to deal with as well,
因为我们也需要处理一些节奏的东西，
so we'll go through it,
所以我们会弹奏它，
one time slowly, then one time a little bit faster,
一次慢的，然后一次快的，
single notes first.
首先是单音符。
One two three four, one,
1 2 3 4 ， 1 ，
three four, rest,
3 4 ，休息，
rest,
休息，
rest rest, one two three four, one two,
休息，休息， 1 2 3 4 ， 1 2 ，
three four,
3 4 ，
three four.
3 4 。
Okay, now let's go through the single notes a little bit faster,
好的，现在让我们把单音符弹得快一点，
one two three four, one,
1 2 3 4 ， 1 ，
three four, rest,
3 4 ，休息，
three four, rest, two three four,
3 4 ，休息， 2 3 4 ，
three four,
3 4 ，
three four.
3 4 。
Great, okay, now let's do the chords on it,
好的，现在我们来弹和弦，
two different strumming patterns we're going to use in this one,
我们要使用两种不同的扫弦模式，
when you, when you have a measure that has two chords in it,
当你有一个小节有两个和弦的时候，
I just want you to go,
我只想让你去做，
down, down up, on the first chord
在第一个和弦，下，下上，
and then the same thing, down, down up, on the second chord,
然后在第二个和弦同样的事情，下，下上，
if you have a measure that's split into two chords per measure.
如果你有一个小节被分成两个和弦，
Okay, so the measures that do that,
好的，在小节中，
in this song have an A and a D in them,
这首歌中有 A 和 D ，
so if we were playing just that measure with A and D,
所以如果我们用 A 和 D 来弹奏这个小节，
it would sound something like this,
它听起来应该是这样的。
ready, go.
准备，开始。
Good, let's do that a couple times through,
好的，让我们再弹几遍，
we'll just repeat it,
我们重复几次，
just that A and D, go,,
只是 A 和 D ，开始，
now, the measure with an E in it,
现在，小节中有一个 E ，
is we're gonna go ahead and use that strumming pattern,
我们要继续使用这个扫弦模式，
down, down up, up, down,
下，下上，上，下，
so on an E chord,
所以，在 E 和弦上，
it would be down, down up, up, down,
它将是下，下上，上，下，
down, down up, up, down.
下，下上，上，下。
Okay, now the song starts off with those pickup notes,
好的，现在歌曲从[拨片音符]开始，
coming into that measure,
从那个小节开始，
starting with the A,
从 A 开始，
so I'm going to start on that measure with the A,
所以我将从 A 开始，
then we'll go from there.
然后我们从那里开始。
One, go slow first, ready go,
1 ，开始先慢一点，准备，开始，
now the full pattern,
现在是完整的模式，
last measure.
最后一个小节。
Okay, now let's play it a little bit quicker,
好的，现在让我们弹奏快一点，
more up to the tempo of the song.
加快歌曲的节奏。
One two three four's,
1 2 3 4 ，
here we go.
干得好。
Very good, okay, now let's do it even faster,
很好，好的，现在让我们再快一次，
one more time, even faster,
再来一次，更快一点，
just to see if we can keep up.
看看我们是否能跟上。
One two, ready, go,
1 2 ，准备，开始，
and that's La Bamba.
这就是 La Bamba 。
Now, there's many more songs in the Jam Along CDs,
现在有更多的歌曲伴在 Jam Along CD 中，
you get a whole lot more practice on these songs,
你可以在这些歌曲上得到更多的练习，
than just one tune that we're able to do here,
而不仅仅这里的一个音调，
and all the practice you can get is going to be well worth your while
你能得到的所有练习将是非常值得的，
in making your strums solid, strong, but still smooth
让你的扫弦坚实，有力，但仍然流畅，
and where you get them fast enough to do, what you need to do.
你足够快地做你需要做的事情。
We'll see you next time.
我们下次再见。